[applause]
>> Hey, congrats, man. We're excited to get
you.
>> [laughter]
>> Hey, I'm going to pass you off to our
owner, David Tepper, okay?
All right, man.
Hey, Lee, how you doing?
Pretty good. Pretty good. Where you
sitting right now?
All right, very good. Good. They excited
about Carolina?
All right,
glad to have you, okay?
I'm going to pass you over here.
Glad to have you. We're going to pass
you over to coach, okay?
What's up, Lee?
Lee, I'm feeling great. I'm better now.
I feel real safe. I feel real safe now
you're coming into the building. Man,
we're fired up to get you in here. This
group is a great group of guys, man.
We're excited. I want you to say hello
to your new coach right here, coach
Washington.
Lee, how you doing, buddy?
Hey, we almost had a hell of a
conversation on Wednesday, huh?
Well, hey, congratulations. I can't wait
for us to get together and start
working.
All right, you have a great night.
Congratulations.
All right, good luck.
>> [applause]
[music]